A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records xFA250
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Foreign Affairs and National Security, 1974-1977; 19; 18.6 Cubic Feet 17 record cartons 4 document boxes
  - Murphy Commission Background Volumes, 1973-1975
    - Background Workbook #7, International Economics, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 428)
    - Background Workbook #9, Public Diplomacy and Support, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 429)
  - National Center for Productivity and Quality of Life, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 430)
    Draft of "Program for Achieving a More Productive Regulatory System," April 16, 1976. Includes NAR's handwritten edits.